[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0714_0101_fieldsoffire",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0714_0101_d_00_container_fieldsoffire",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0714_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0714_0101_fieldsoffire_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0714_0101_fieldsoffire_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0714_0101_fieldsoffire_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0714_0101_fieldsoffire_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0714_0101_fieldsoffire_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0714_0101_fieldsoffire_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0714_0101_fieldsoffire_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "ShateredMtnArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0719_0101_reflectionsmountainheart",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0719_0101_d_00_container_reflectionsmountainheart",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_10",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0719_0101_reflectionsmountainheart_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0719_0101_reflectionsmountainheart_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0719_0101_reflectionsmountainheart_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0719_0101_reflectionsmountainheart_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0719_0101_reflectionsmountainheart_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0719_0101_reflectionsmountainheart_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0719_0101_reflectionsmountainheart_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0713_0101_explorerift",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0713_0101_d_00_container_explorerift",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0713_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0713_0101_explorerift_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0713_0101_explorerift_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0713_0101_explorerift_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0713_0101_explorerift_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0713_0101_explorerift_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0713_0101_explorerift_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0713_0101_explorerift_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "ShateredMtnArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0715_0102_luckonlylends",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0715_0102_d_00_container_luckonlylends",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0714_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0715_0102_luckonlylends_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0715_0102_luckonlylends_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0715_0102_luckonlylends_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0715_0102_luckonlylends_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0715_0102_luckonlylends_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0715_0102_luckonlylends_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0715_0102_luckonlylends_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "ShateredMtnArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0715_0101_varietiesofheat",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0715_0101_d_00_container_varietiesofheat",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0715_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0715_0101_varietiesofheat_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0715_0101_varietiesofheat_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0715_0101_varietiesofheat_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0715_0101_varietiesofheat_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0715_0101_varietiesofheat_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0715_0101_varietiesofheat_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0715_0101_varietiesofheat_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "ShateredMtnArc1"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0716_0101_malevolentofferings",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0716_0101_d_00_container_malevolentofferings",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0713_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0716_0101_malevolentofferings_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0716_0101_malevolentofferings_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0716_0101_malevolentofferings_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0716_0101_malevolentofferings_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0716_0101_malevolentofferings_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0716_0101_malevolentofferings_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0716_0101_malevolentofferings_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "ShateredMtnArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0712_0101_layerspastandpresent",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0712_0101_d_00_container_layerspastandpresent",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0712_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0712_0101_layerspastandpresent_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0712_0101_layerspastandpresent_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0712_0101_layerspastandpresent_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0712_0101_layerspastandpresent_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0712_0101_layerspastandpresent_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0712_0101_layerspastandpresent_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0712_0101_layerspastandpresent_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "ShateredMtnArc3"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0718_0102_humble",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0718_0102_d_00_container_humble",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0718_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0718_0102_humble_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0718_0102_humble_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0718_0102_humble_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0718_0102_humble_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0718_0102_humble_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0718_0102_humble_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0718_0102_humble_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "ShateredMtnArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0718_0101_guardian",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0718_0101_d_00_container_guardian",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0718_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_09",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0718_0101_guardian_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0718_0101_guardian_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0718_0101_guardian_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0718_0101_guardian_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0718_0101_guardian_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0718_0101_guardian_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0718_0101_guardian_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "ShateredMtnArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0717_0101_myrkgardarena",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0717_0101_d_00_container_myrkgardarena",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0717_0101_mykgardarena_success",
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0717_0101_myrkgardarena_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0717_0101_myrkgardarena_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0717_0101_myrkgardarena_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0717_0101_myrkgardarena_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0717_0101_myrkgardarena_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0717_0101_myrkgardarena_complete_available_response",
        "ReleaseEventTags": "CANCELLED"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0719_0201_madakisstratagem",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0719_0201_d_00_container_madakisstratagem",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0719_0201_madakisstratagem_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@0719_0201_madakisstratagem_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0719_0201_madakisstratagem_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0719_0201_madakisstratagem_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0719_0201_madakisstratagem_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0719_0201_madakisstratagem_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0719_0201_madakisstratagem_complete_available_response",
        "QuestArcTag": "GreatCleaveArc2"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0714_0105_baetylusheadpiece",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0714_0105_d_00_container_baetylusheadpiece",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0714_Watcher",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_Lazarus_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0714_0105_baetylusheadpiece_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0714_0105_baetylusheadpiece_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0714_0105_baetylusheadpiece_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0714_0105_baetylusheadpiece_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0714_0105_baetylusheadpiece_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0714_0105_baetylusheadpiece_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0714_0105_baetylusheadpiece_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0718_0103_ultimatedefense",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0718_0103_d_00_container_ultimatedefense",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0718_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "07_Quest_Garden_12",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0718_0103_ultimatedefense_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0718_0103_ultimatedefense_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0718_0103_ultimatedefense_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0718_0103_ultimatedefense_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0718_0103_ultimatedefense_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0718_0103_ultimatedefense_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0718_0103_ultimatedefense_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0101_TF_00",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0101_TF_00_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TwilightsFall_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0101_TF_00_success",
        "ObjectiveReward": "0721_0101_BW_00",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0101_TF_00_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0101_TF_00_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0721_0101_TF_00_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0721_0101_TF_00_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0721_0101_TF_00_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0721_0101_TF_00_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0102_TF_01",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0102_TF_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TwilightsFall_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0102_TF_01_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0102_TF_01_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0102_TF_01_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0721_0102_TF_01_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0721_0102_TF_01_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0721_0102_TF_01_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0103_TF_02",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0103_TF_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TwilightsFall_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0103_TF_02_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0103_TF_02_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0103_TF_02_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0721_0103_TF_02_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0721_0103_TF_02_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0721_0103_TF_02_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0104_TF_03",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0104_TF_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TwilightsFall_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0104_TF_03_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0104_TF_03_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0104_TF_03_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0721_0104_TF_03_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0721_0104_TF_03_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0721_0104_TF_03_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0105_TF_04",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0105_TF_04_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TwilightsFall_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0105_TF_04_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0105_TF_04_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0105_TF_04_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0721_0105_TF_04_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0721_0105_TF_04_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0721_0105_TF_04_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0106_TF_05",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0106_TF_05_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TwilightsFall_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0106_TF_05_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0106_TF_05_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0106_TF_05_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0721_0106_TF_05_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0721_0106_TF_05_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0721_0106_TF_05_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0107_TF_06",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0107_TF_06_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TwilightsFall_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0107_TF_06_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0107_TF_06_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0107_TF_06_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0721_0107_TF_06_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0721_0107_TF_06_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0721_0107_TF_06_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0108_TF_07",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0108_TF_07_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TwilightsFall_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0108_TF_07_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0108_TF_07_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0108_TF_07_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0721_0108_TF_07_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0721_0108_TF_07_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0721_0108_TF_07_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0109_TF_08",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0109_TF_08_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_TwilightsFall_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0109_TF_08_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0109_TF_08_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0109_TF_08_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0721_0109_TF_08_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0721_0109_TF_08_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0721_0109_TF_08_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0101_BW_00",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0101_BW_00_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_BoundlessWard_00",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0101_BW_00_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0101_BW_00_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0101_BW_00_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0720_0101_BW_00_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0721_0101_BW_00_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0721_0101_BW_00_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0102_BW_01",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0102_BW_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_BoundlessWard_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0102_BW_01_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0102_BW_01_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0102_BW_01_objective_desc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0103_BW_02",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0103_BW_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_BoundlessWard_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0103_BW_02_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0103_BW_02_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0103_BW_02_objective_desc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0104_BW_03",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0104_BW_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_BoundlessWard_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0104_BW_03_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0104_BW_03_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0104_BW_03_objective_desc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0721_0105_BW_04",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0721_0105_BW_04_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_BoundlessWard_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0721_0105_BW_04_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0721_0105_BW_04_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0721_0105_BW_04_objective_desc"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0720_0101_HS_00",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0720_0101_HS_00_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Heavensplitter_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0720_0101_HS_00_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0720_0101_HS_00_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0720_0101_HS_00_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0720_0101_HS_00_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0720_0101_HS_00_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0720_0101_HS_00_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0720_0101_HS_00_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0720_0102_HS_01",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0720_0102_HS_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Heavensplitter_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0720_0102_HS_01_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0720_0102_HS_01_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0720_0102_HS_01_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0720_0103_HS_02",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0720_0103_HS_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Heavensplitter_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0720_0103_HS_02_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0720_0103_HS_02_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0720_0103_HS_02_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0720_0104_HS_03",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0720_0104_HS_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Heavensplitter_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0720_0104_HS_03_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0720_0104_HS_03_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0720_0104_HS_03_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0720_0105_HS_04",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0720_0105_HS_04_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Heavensplitter_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0720_0105_HS_04_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0720_0105_HS_04_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0720_0105_HS_04_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0720_0106_HS_05",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0720_0106_HS_05_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Heavensplitter_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0720_0106_HS_05_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0720_0106_HS_05_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0720_0106_HS_05_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0720_0107_HS_06",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0720_0107_HS_06_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Heavensplitter_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0720_0107_HS_06_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0720_0107_HS_06_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0720_0107_HS_06_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0720_0108_HS_07",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0720_0108_HS_07_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Heavensplitter_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0720_0108_HS_07_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0720_0108_HS_07_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0720_0108_HS_07_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0720_0109_HS_08",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0720_0109_HS_08_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Heavensplitter_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0720_0109_HS_08_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0720_0109_HS_08_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0720_0109_HS_08_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0722_0101_FL_00",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0722_0101_FL_00_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0719_Ranger",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Frozenlament_00",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "07_Quest_11",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0722_0101_FL_00_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0722_0101_FL_00_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0722_0101_FL_00_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0722_0101_FL_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0722_0101_FL_00_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0722_0101_FL_00_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0722_0101_FL_00_complete_available_response"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0722_0102_FL_01",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0722_0102_FL_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Frozenlament_01",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0722_0102_FL_01_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0722_0101_FL_01_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0722_0101_FL_01_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0722_0103_FL_02",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0722_0103_FL_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Frozenlament_02",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0722_0103_FL_02_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0722_0101_FL_02_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0722_0101_FL_02_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0722_0104_FL_03",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0722_0104_FL_03_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Frozenlament_03",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0722_0104_FL_03_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0722_0101_FL_03_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0722_0101_FL_03_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0722_0105_FL_04",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0722_0105_FL_04_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Frozenlament_04",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0722_0105_FL_04_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0722_0101_FL_04_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0722_0101_FL_04_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0722_0106_FL_05",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0722_0106_FL_05_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Frozenlament_05",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0722_0106_FL_05_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0722_0101_FL_05_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0722_0101_FL_05_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0722_0107_FL_06",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0722_0107_FL_06_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Frozenlament_06",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0722_0107_FL_06_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0722_0101_FL_06_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0722_0101_FL_06_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0722_0108_FL_07",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0722_0108_FL_07_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Frozenlament_07",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0722_0108_FL_07_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0722_0101_FL_07_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0722_0101_FL_07_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0722_0109_FL_08",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": false,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "0722_0109_FL_08_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
        "AchievementId": "WeaponQuest_Frozenlament_08",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0722_0109_FL_08_success",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0722_0101_FL_08_objective_title",
        "Description": "@0722_0101_FL_08_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_07_PVP_Spy_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_07_PVP_Spy_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_07_PVP_Poach_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_07_PVP_Poach_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_07_PVP_Control_Marauder_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_07_PVP_Control_Marauder_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_07_PVP_Spy_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_07_PVP_Spy_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_07_PVP_Poach_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_07_PVP_Poach_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_07_PVP_Control_Syndicate_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_07_PVP_Control_Syndicate_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_07_PVP_Spy_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_07_PVP_Spy_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_07_PVP_Poach_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_07_PVP_Poach_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_07_PVP_Control_Covenant_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": true,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "FM_07_PVP_Control_Covenant_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "Repeatable": "1",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0701_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0701_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0702_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0702_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0703_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0703_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0704_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0704_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0705_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0705_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0706_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0706_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0707_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0707_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0701_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0701_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0702_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0702_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0703_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0703_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0704_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0704_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0705_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0705_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0706_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0706_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0707_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0707_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0701_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0701_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0702_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0702_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0703_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0703_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0704_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0704_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0705_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0705_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0706_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0706_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0707_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0707_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0761_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0761_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0762_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0762_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0763_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0763_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0764_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0764_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0765_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0765_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_0766_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_0766_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0761_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0761_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0762_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0762_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0763_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0763_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0764_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0764_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0765_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0765_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_S_0766_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_S_0766_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0761_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0761_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0762_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0762_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0763_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0763_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0764_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0764_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0765_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0765_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_C_0766_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_C_0766_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_07_H_01_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_07_H_01_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "FM_07_H_02_objective",
        "Type": "Mission",
        "DifficultyLevel": 0,
        "FlagPvp": false,
        "CanBeShared": true,
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "FM_07_H_02_container",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 7,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true
    }
]